right now and %uh
nap in 10 minutes in fact no Jess isn't good at everything out there anyway but
we want to do is going to focus on what no jess is good at
so we're gonna build a web application first things first
we need to get ourselves and tools to work with so use
the node package manager to do that the N CAM repository
is a collection have third party software that is available for everyone
to use
we're gonna make ourselves
an application folder called ap sprint and we want to work with is well as many
frameworks out there I'm gonna pick one
something to get started with and I'm going to
and p.m. install express at a particular version
just because I know this version works
there better ways of managing application which will see later
but this look it up in going because we'll be able to create ourselves
a web framework without having to actually build everything from scratch
will likely notice that we have a node modules folder one thing I think and Kim
got really really right
was it opposed to having a centralized location for all of our packages get
installed to
by default packages are installed into the local directory
which means that we have all the rights to use them and they don't collide with
other people's packages
let's make use I've express
to create a project scaffolding
not that I can spell that would go yes I want to continue in my non empty
directory:
now this is where we can see how node JS and teamwork
excellently I have a package that Jason folder which will take a look at later
this allows me to manage dependencies I love my
program where I'm at I can do a simple NPM install
everything I need gets downloaded
and get a cup coffee
can hang out I can pretend my code is compiling
there we go we're done and now we have enough to do it
basic lol program and make sure everything is working most programs in
node
actually are begun by running the note interpreter on a particular
file we do that whether application
we run note on tap that JS expressed by default runs on port 3000
and less is tech test this out here hello world expressed welcome to express
we have achieved